# [
#     {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]
question_data =[
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The two atomic bombs dropped on Japan by the United States in August 1945 were named &#039;Little Man&#039; and &#039;Fat Boy&#039;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The word &quot;Inception&quot; came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The &quot;Pepe&quot; meme originated from a comic drawn by Matt Furie called &quot;Boy&#039;s Club&quot;?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack &quot;Kamehameha&quot; in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "George W. Bush lost the popular vote in the 2004 United States presidential election.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Cats have whiskers under their legs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In World War ll, Great Britian used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert Hitler away from Normandy\/D-day landing.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nickelodeon rejected the pilot to Adventure Time.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ", "correct_answer": "False",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Helen Clark was the 37th Prime Minister of Australia.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The song Scatman&#039;s World was released after Scatman (Ski-Ba-Bop-Ba-Dop-Bop).",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The title of the 1969 film &quot;Krakatoa, East_of Java&quot; is incorrect, as Krakatoa is in fact west of Java.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
